export const holidayData = [
  { id: 1, variant: "click", front: "Bad Special Effects", back: "Take a sip" },
  {
    id: 2,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Melissa Joan Hart",
    back: "Take a sip",
  },
  { id: 3, variant: "click", front: "Baking Fight", back: "Take a sip" },
  {
    id: 4,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Related to Santa",
    back: "Finish your Drink",
  },
  { id: 5, variant: "click", front: "Candace Cameron", back: "Take a sip" },
  {
    id: 6,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Workaholic",
    back: "Give a Sip",
  },
  { id: 7, variant: "click", front: "Ghost", back: "Social" },
  { id: 8, variant: "click", front: "Precocious Child", back: "Take a Sip" },
  { id: 9, variant: "click", front: "Magical Weirdo", back: "Be Magical" },
  { id: 10, variant: "click", front: "One Tree Hill", back: "Take a sip" },
  { id: 11, variant: "click", front: "Car Trouble", back: "Give a sip" },
  {
    id: 12,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Forced to kiss - sparks fly",
    back: "Take a sip",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Character is cynical about Christmas",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Need to Save Family Business",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  { id: 15, variant: "click", front: "Time Travel", back: "Take a shot" },

  {
    id: 16,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Secretly Royal",
    back: "Finish your Drink",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Lead Partakes in Tradition",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Plot-driving Breakup",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Romantic Fall in the Snow",
    back: "Give a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    variant: "click",
    front: "In need of a miracle",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 21,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Awe-struck by lead in underwhelming dress",
    back: "Social",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    variant: "click",
    front: "10 yr-old Speaks Like Toddler",
    back: "Take a Shot",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Bad Foreign Accent",
    back: "Take a Shot",
  },
  { id: 24, variant: "click", front: "Decorating Montage", back: "Social" },
  {
    id: 25,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Christmas Themed Name",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  { id: 26, variant: "click", front: "Distracting Extras", back: "Take a Sip" },
  { id: 27, variant: "click", front: "Xmas Eve Deadline", back: "Take a Sip" },
  {
    id: 28,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Wink - wise old guy is SANTA!",
    back: "Take a Shot",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Eccentric Grandparent",
    back: "Take a Sip",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    variant: "click",
    front: "Horse Drawn Carriage Ride",
    back: "Social",
  },
];
